Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Botany Records 1882-1972
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1891-1936
  - Subseries 6: 3"x4" Glass Negatives
    - AEP-MIN174, Dunes advancing into Hamlin Lake, Ludington, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN175, Mesophytic forest on a dune crater opening toward Hamlin Lake, Ludington, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN176, Partially fixed dunes north of the lighthouse, Ludington, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN177, Partially fixed dunes north of the lighthouse, Ludington, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN178, Dune complex behind the lighthouse at Big Sable Point, Ludington, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN206, Pinus banksiana, Pentwater, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN207, Quercus velutina trunk, Pentwater, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN208, Zonation of Carex, Chamaedaphne calyculata, and Pinus banksiana in a dry bog, Pentwater, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN210, Looking south at Ammophila breviligulata on a new dune, Pinus strobus, etc. on old dunes, north of Pentwater, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN211, Birds-eye view looking across the north end of Bass Lake, Pentwater, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN212, Advancing dune covering a mesophytic forest, Sawyer, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN213, Advancing dune showing crushed Beech and Maple, Sawyer, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN217, Advancing dune covering a mesophytic forest, Sawyer, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN218, Eroding stratified gravel cliff with perched dunes, west shore of South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN219, Highest dune above forest of Acer, Abies, Thuja, etc., South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN220, Shore cliffs with foredune on depositing shore, Betula, Thuja, and Abies near a lighthouse, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN221, Thuja occidentalis trunk, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN222, Clay shore cliffs with Thuja occidentalis, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN223, Clay shore cliffs with Thuja occidentalis, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN224, Thuja occidentalis graveyard, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN225, Up-wind sweep, high dunes and gravel cliffs, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN226, Lighthouse, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN227, Lighthouse, South Fox Island, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN228, University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class, Warren Woods, Three Oaks, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN229, Showing the size of an Elm with buttressed base, Warren Woods, Three Oaks, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN230, Fagus, Warren Woods, Three Oaks, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN231, Fraxinus nigra trunk, Warren Woods, Three Oaks, Michigan (Box 63)
    - AEP-MIN232, Platanus occidentalis on a floodplain, Warren Woods, Three Oaks, Michigan (Box 63)
    - Item 74: Washington (Box 63)
  - Subseries 7: Lantern Slides
    - Alabama, AEP-ALS1, Close view of a Pinus palustris forest, Baldwin County, Alabama AEP-ALS2, Stand of Pinus palustris and Pinus taeda, Choctaw County, Alabama AEP-ALS3, Nyssa sylvatica, Liquidambar styraciflua, and Pinus taeda, Jefferson County, Alabama AEP-ALS4, Pinus palustris being boxed for turpentine, Mobile County, Alabama AEP-ALS5, Pinus echinata and Quercus stellata, Sumter County, Alabama AEP-ALS6, Pinus palustris forest, Jasper, Alabama AEP-ALS7, Pinus taeda boxed for turpentine, Washington County, Alabama AEP-ALS8, Alabama AEP-ALS9, Alabama AEP-ALS10, Alabama (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 1)
    - Alaska, AEP-AKS1, Barnacles growing on rocks which were displaced in 1899 by uplift, Disenchantment Bay, Alaska AEP-AKS2, Dryas drummondii growing on glaciated rock surfaces and thin ground moraine, Glacier Bay, Alaska AEP-AKS3, Dryas drummondii enclosed by a quadrat positioned at the ice limit of 1879, Glacier Bay, Alaska AEP-AKS5, Alpine krummholz, Juneau, Alaska AEP-AKS6, Mountain tundra and snowfields near Juneau, Alaska AEP-AKS7, Bushes growing atop two Totem Poles within a group standing at old Kasaan, Alaska AEP-AKS8, Totem Poles at old Kasaan, Alaska AEP-AKS9, Grouping of Mortuary poles at old Kasaan, Alaska (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 1)
    - Arizona, AEP-AZS1, Petrified log and trees in a ravine, Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS2, Logs in the Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS3, Logs in the Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS4, Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS5, Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS6, Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS7, Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS8, Petrified Forest National Park, Adamana, Arizona AEP-AZS9, Summer in the Petrified Forest National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS11, Bright Angel Point, Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS12, Mojave Indian dwellings at Canyon Diablo, Arizona AEP-AZS13, Close view of a single Berberis fremontii shrub at Cedar Ranch, Arizona AEP-AZS14, Showing the size of a single Juniperus occidentalis, Cedar Ranch, Arizona AEP-AZS15, Border between forest and prairie, Cedar Ranch, Arizona AEP-AZS16, Mesquite bosque with Atriplex polycarpa and Prosopis velutina along an irrigation ditch, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS17, Carnegia gigantea, Opuntia fulgida, Acacia sp., and winter annuals, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS18, Larrea tridentata, Prosopis velutina, and Lycium, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS19, Lycium sp. at Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS20, Lycium sp. at Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS21, Opuntia fulgida, Ferocactus wislizeni, Parkinsonia microphylla, and winter annuals, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS22, Opuntia fulgida, Prosopis velutina, and Atriplex polycarpa on deep valley soil, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS23, Opuntia versicolor or fulgida, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS24, Mesquite bosque with Prosopis velutina and Atriplex polycarpa, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS25, Prosopis velutina and Atriplex sp., Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS26, Sheep grazing near Prosopis velutina, Opuntia fulgida, and winter annuals, Coolidge, Arizona AEP-AZS27, Men planting Parthenium argentatum at Continental, Arizona AEP-AZS28, Beds of Parthenium argentatum at Continental, Arizona AEP-AZS29, Irrigation pipe for Parthenium argentatum at Continental, Arizona AEP-AZS30, On Agassiz Peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS31, On Agassiz Peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS32, Near the top of San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS33, Cliff dwellings in Walnut Canyon near Flagstaff, Arizona AEP-AZS34, Cliff dwellings in Walnut Canyon near Flagstaff, Arizona AEP-AZS37, View of Cactuses along the Grand Canyon in Arizona AEP-AZS38, Coleogyne at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS39, Ephedra at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS40, Close view of Ephedra at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS41, Ephedra at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS43, Close view of a single Juniperus monosperma at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS44, Juniperus monosperma and Pinus edulis at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS45, Juniperus monosperma, Pinus edulis, and Pinus ponderosa at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS46, Mesquite and Chaparral at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS47, Invasion of Pinus and Picea into Populus tremuloides at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS48, Pinus edulis at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS49, Harriet Cowles in a stand of Pinus edulis near Canyon Inn, Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS50, Pinus edulis and Juniperus at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS51, Pinus edulis and Juniperus scopulorum at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS52, Pinus edulis, Juniperus utahensis, Artemisia tridentata, and Juniperus monosperma at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS53, Pinus edulis, Juniperus utahensis, and Yucca baccata at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS54, Pinus edulis and Juniperus utahensis at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS55, Pinus edulis, Yucca baccata, and Cowania, at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS56, Pinus edulis and Yucca baccata at the south rim of the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS57, Pinus ponderosa with an undergrowth of Quercus gambelii at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS58, Pinus ponderosa at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS59, Pinus ponderosa, Juniperus utahensis, Pinus edulis, and Juniperus monosperma at the south rim of the Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS60, Effects of snow on Quaking Aspen, Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS61, General view of an eroding landscape dotted by small trees at the Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS62, Grand Canyon of the Colorado River, Arizona AEP-AZS63, Grand Canyon of the Colorado River, Arizona AEP-AZS64, Grand Canyon of the Colorado River, Arizona AEP-AZS65, Grand Canyon of the Colorado River, Arizona AEP-AZS66, Grand Canyon, Arizona AEP-AZS67, North rim, Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS68, Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS69, North rim, Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS84, Native American in tribal dress at Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona AEP-AZS85, Pinus edulis, Artemisia, and Ephedra on the Kaibab Plateau, Arizona AEP-AZS87, Pinus scopulorum in the Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS88, Pinus scopulorum at VT Ranch, Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS89, Pinus scopulorum and Populus tremuloides, a zonal jumble in the Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS90, Populus tremuloides, Picea engelmannii, and Pinus scopulorum in the Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS91, Robinia neomexicana in the Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS92, Deer in the Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS93, Deer in the Kaibab National Forest, Arizona AEP-AZS97, Pinus monophylla in broad sclerophyll scrub, Miami, Arizona AEP-AZS98, Broad sclerophyll scrub, Miami, Arizona AEP-AZS99, General view of Humphreys Peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS100, Quercus reticulata and Quercus hypoleuca on the east face of Mt. Lemmon, Arizona AEP-AZS101, Bouteloua and Hilaria with Quercus emoryi, Quercus arizonica, and Yucca spp., Nogales, Arizona AEP-AZS102, Bouteloua and Hilaria with Quercus sp. and Yucca spp., Nogales, Arizona AEP-AZS103, Overgrazed Bouteloua and Hilaria with Yucca, Oracle, Arizona AEP-AZS104, Opuntia fulgida at Oracle Junction, Arizona AEP-AZS105, Parkinsonia, Prosopis, Carnegia gigantea, Rumex, and Opuntia in the Santa Catalina Mountains near Oracle Junction, Arizona AEP-AZS106, Prosopis velutina and Rumex in the Santa Catalina Mountains near Oracle Junction, Arizona AEP-AZS107, Painted Desert, Arizona AEP-AZS108, Nolina and Quercus emoryi growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria, Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS109, Desert to grassland to woodland transition of Quercus and Juniperus growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria, Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS110, Quercus emoryi, Quercus arizonica, and Nolina growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria, Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS111, Quercus spp. and Nolina growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria, Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS112, Quercus spp. and Prosopis velutina growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria, Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS113, Bouteloua and Hilaria with Quercus spp., Nolina, and Yucca, Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS114, Quercus spp. and Prosopis velutina growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria south of Patagonia, Arizona AEP-AZS115, Between Patagonia and Nogales, Arizona a view of Prosopis velutina and Quercus spp. growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria AEP-AZS116, Between Patagonia and Vail, Arizona a view of Prosopis velutina invading Bouteloua and Hilaria AEP-AZS117, Between Patagonia and Vail, Arizona a view of Prosopis velutina, Nolina, and Quercus spp. growing in Bouteloua and Hilaria AEP-AZS118, Agave sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS119, Broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS120, Quercus, Rhus, Arctostaphylos, Rhamnus, and Ceanothus in broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS121, Mammillaria sp. and Opuntia sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS122, Opuntia sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS123, Opuntia sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS124, Pinus ponderosa at Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS125, Pinus ponderosa and Arctostaphylos in Chaparral undergrowth, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS126, Pinus ponderosa forest with a broad sclerophyll scrub undergrowth, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS127, Pinus ponderosa, Quercus spp., Rhus, and Arctostaphylos in broad sclerophyll scrub, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS128, Quercus sp. and broad sclerophyll scrub growing on northern and southern mountain slopes, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS129, Quercus sp. and Pinus ponderosa in broad sclerophyll scrub growing on northern and southern mountain slopes, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS130, Quercus sp. and Pinus ponderosa in broad sclerophyll scrub growing on northern and southern mountain slopes, Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS131, Arctostaphylos spp. and Quercus spp. in broad sclerophyll scrub south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS132, Quercus on the north slope of a hill with broad sclerophyll scrub in the foreground south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS133, View of broad sclerophyll scrub south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS134, Southern desert scrub transition, Franseria to Arctostaphylos and Chaparral south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS135, Glossopetalon growing south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS136, Juniperus sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS137, Quercus sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub on a north slope south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS138, Quercus sp. in broad sclerophyll scrub on snow-covered northern slopes south of Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS139, Area of transition from Chaparral and Arctostaphylos to Bouteloua and Agropyron between Prescott and Williams, Arizona AEP-AZS140, Juniperus invading Bouteloua gracilis and Agropyron smithii in an overgrazed area between Williams and Prescott, Arizona AEP-AZS143, Juniperus pachyphlaea invading Bouteloua gracilis as a result of overgrazing between Prescott and Williams, Arizona AEP-AZS144, Larrea tridentata and winter annuals on a plain, Rillito, Arizona AEP-AZS145, Opuntia fulgida or versicolor and Larrea tridentata in a wash, Rillito, Arizona AEP-AZS146, Several flowering Agave plants, Rio Verde, Arizona AEP-AZS147, Pinus and Agave, Rio Verde, Arizona AEP-AZS148, Close view of several Juniperus, Rio Verde, Arizona AEP-AZS149, Pinyon forest in the Rio Verde Valley, Arizona AEP-AZS150, Carnegia gigantea, Crater Lake, Arizona AEP-AZS151, Silt masses from a flood on the Salt River, Arizona AEP-AZS152, Pseudotsuga on San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS153, Primula parryi in an alpine rill and meadow, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS154, Tree line on San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS155, Tree line on Agassiz Peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS156, Advance of timber on a cirque, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS157, Crags, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS158, View from the west, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS159, View of the peaks, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS160, View of a low peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS161, Snowfield on Agassiz Peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS162, Looking down from a snowfield on Agassiz Peak, San Francisco Mountain, Arizona AEP-AZS163, Acacia in desert grassland, Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS164, Fouquieria and Agave in a southern desert grassland, Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS165, Alnus and Populus in Marshall Gulch, Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS166, Arbutus arizonica in the Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS167, Baccharis, Bidens, and Quercus along a dry streambed in the Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS168, Carnegia gigantea, a close view of several plants in the Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS169, Reproduction of Carnegia gigantea among Fouquieria and Opuntia, Santa Catalina Mountains, Arizona AEP-AZS170, Carnegia gigantea in the Santa Catalina Mountain
    - Arkansas, AEP-ARP1, Beehives on stilts in a flood region, Manila, Arkansas AEP-ARS1, Taxodium distichum on earthquake timber at Bagwells Lake, Arkansas AEP-ARS2, Phoradendron in a mesophytic forest, Bertig, Arkansas AEP-ARS3, Taxodium distichum, a view of a forest at the fringe of a swamp, Bertig, Arkansas AEP-ARS4, Trunk of a Fraxinus profunda, Big Lake, Arkansas AEP-ARS5, Overturned Populus deltoides showing its roots, Big Lake, Arkansas AEP-ARS6, Salix and Nelumbo, Big Lake, Arkansas AEP-ARS7, View of a Populus deltoides trunk in a bottom forest, Blytheville, Arkansas AEP-ARS8, Arundinaria forming a canebrake, Blytheville, Arkansas AEP-ARS9, Erosion at Crowleys Ridge, Arkansas AEP-ARS10, Taxodium forest on the edge of a swamp prairie two miles north of Blytheville, Arkansas AEP-ARS11, View of anold Cypress stump, Flat Lake, Arkansas AEP-ARS12, C. M. Bourlands homestead two miles north of Blytheville, Arkansas AEP-ARS14, View of a Liquidambar styraciflua trunk, Moon Lake, Arkansas AEP-ARS15, Quercus spp. in the Ouachita Mountains, Arkansas AEP-ARS16, View of a Quercus texana trunk, Pettyville, Arkansas AEP-ARS17, Submerged earthquake timber, Big Lake, Pettyville, Arkansas AEP-ARS18, Jonesboro, Lake City, and Eastern railroad track with ties split from trees, Pettyville, Arkansas AEP-ARS19, Good bark study of a Quercus lyrata, an 1847 Witness Tree, Arkansas AEP-ARS20, Close view of an Ulmus americana, an 1846 Witness Tree, Arkansas AEP-ARS21, Arkansas River in flood, Arkansas AEP-ARS22, Cast of a blaze in young growth Taxodium, Arkansas AEP-ARS23, Field of Cotton, Arkansas (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 4)